crackingpatching.com 2018-10-06

# Privacy Policy - CrackingPatching

Rate This Post:

Loading...

 **Crackingpatching.com** websites (collectively “ **https://crackingpatching.com** ” in this document) refer to site based on WordPress platform and this website **don’t have any sub-domain** and **don’t have any forum** for past plenty of months.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, https://crackingpatching.com collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. https://crackingpatching.com’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how https://crackingpatching.com’s visitors use this website.

https://crackingpatching.com also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, email addresses, and name (optional) that can people enter to receive emails regarding new post published on our website. Even it’s not necessary to subscribe through Email address to enter personal information it depends upon personal choice of visitor. https://crackingpatching.com does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to https://crackingpatching.com choose to interact with https://crackingpatching.com in ways that require https://crackingpatching.com to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that https://crackingpatching.com gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors if he/she wants to receive email notification regarding new posts published or wants to post comment on any post published based on his/ her experience to help other visitors to understand experience of already visited users. In each case, https://crackingpatching.com collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with https://crackingpatching.com. https://crackingpatching.com does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

https://crackingpatching.com may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to this website. For instance, https://crackingpatching.com may reveal how many times a particular visitor visits a page, or say which post is most popular as compared to others so website https://crackingpatching.com can rank its posts based on its popularity on the basis of number of times users visits a particular page. However, https://crackingpatching.com does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

https://crackingpatching.com discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of this website Administrator and Moderators that (i) need to know that information in order to process to help or publish relevant content which people are demanding more often. Currently we don’t’ offer any registration even in forum or on our website collectively because we closed website forum couple of months ago due to some technical reasons and spam registrations.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. https://crackingpatching.com don’t use any kind of cookies information coz it’s not relevant to our website’s nature If any.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, https://crackingpatching.com may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in https://crackingpatching.com’s sole discretion. https://crackingpatching.com encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

**Thanks for Understanding and cooperation**
